SAMUEL LEVY

Berwyn, PA 19312

Phone: 610-420-9311 | Email: slevy239@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/samuel-d-levy/ | Github: github.com/Slevy239 | Portfolio: portfolio-

levy.herokuapp.com/

SUMMARY

Motivated Full Stack Web Developer with a strong background in communications. Brings hard work and dedication inspired by encountering problems and finding an effective solution. Strong collaboration skills from previous professional experience. Excels at customer service and finding solutions to every situation in the workplace.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS, JQuery, NodeJS, Express, Firebase, MySQL, MongoDB, Handlebar.js, ReactJS

PROJECTS

iPlaylist | Github.com/Slevy239/iPlaylist | iplaylist-2019.herokuapp.com

- Community based music playlist application
- Responsible for front-end logic and display
- Javascript, JQuery Node Js, Passport, Handlebars, MySQL

Friend Finder | Github.com/Slevy239/FriendFinder | the-friend-finder-2019.herokuapp.com

- Survey application, which matches the user with a person in an API based on responses
- Built and designed entire project
- Javascript, JQuery, Express

Eat a Burger! | Github.com/ Slevy239/burger | eat-a-burger-2019.herokuapp.com

- A MySQL based application that allows for CRUD operations on page elements.
- Built and designed entire project
- Javascript, Node JS, Handlebars, Express, MySQL

EXPERIENCE

Scheduling Specialist

2018 - 2019

Quench USA INC.

King of Prussia, Pa

Handled technician scheduling for large metropolitan markets around the U.S. Primarily used spreadsheets to handle and manage schedule data. Worked in groups to tackle appointment backlog across multiple markets. Relayed information about products to technicians and customers. Gave customer support when issues were escalated beyond the technician.

Pharmacy Technician

2012 - 2017

Paoli Pharmacy Berwyn, Pa

Managed inventory and prescriptions through pharmacy software. Assisted pharmacist with filling prescriptions. Aided customers with over-the-counter products. Built relationships with return patrons. Learned fundamental customer service and communication skills.

Server / Bartender

2017 - Current

Crowded Castle Brewing Company

Berwyn, Pa

Promote, manage and book musicians for private events. Track inventory with Microsoft Excel.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA

2018 - 2019

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Bachelor of the Arts in Communication: Villanova University, Villanova, PA

2014 - 2018

Focus in Media Studies. Produced audio for 'Sankofa', a student run film production that won Gold at the 2019 Student Academy Awards for Documentary.